He won't do it, he doesn't get it...
What's not to get!? Let me talk to him...
Alright but, ah, he's in a bad mood.
You can do this, you're perfect! The script is perfect!
Just believe in the concept.
Just look at the camera, and let it out.
Breathe, and release...
Don't read the script, be the script!
Breathe, and release!
Just let it all out...
Find your motivation!
Just roar, don't hold back...
Roarrrrr!!!
Roar! roar! roarrrr!
And a-r-t-i-c-u-l-a-t-e!
This... this isn't, this isn't...
[Cat yawns and leaves the set]
- Maybe cat videos aren't the best videos for your Enterprise Video Channel...
Need help programming your organization's video channel? And making content that people really want to watch?
Tune-in to Kaltura's "What's On" Webinar
Join Jordan Berman, CEO of Office Engagement Network
and me, David P. Kronmiller, host and creator of I Went To Film School So You Don't Have To
In an entertaining and informative webinar that demystifies how to program your video channel
It's time to unleash your inner Spielberg...
Or Sofia Coppola...
..